A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A94), 1966-1994; 1.20; 217.2 Cubic Feet; Record cartons R2728-R2895, R2880A, R2896-R2902, R2905, R2906-R2911, R9402 and R9403.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 90099 A 87 - Great Lakes Theater Festival - Adrienne Kennedy's "Ohio State Murders", 1991-1992 (Box R2750)
    - RF 90099 A 88 - Highways - "The Warrior Council", 1991-1992 (Box R2750)
    - RF 90100 - Smithsonian Institution - Tropical rainforests exhibit in Latin America, 1990-1992 (Box R2750)
    - RF 90107 - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) - Voting Rights, 1980-1993; 3 files. (Box R2750)
    - RF 90109 - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - "Childhood in America" documentary, 1988-1992 (Box R2751)
    - RF 90110 A 19 - New Jersey Department of Education, State of - School's orientation of Comer's program, 1991-1992 (Box R2751)
    - RF 90116 - National Public Radio - News and information programming, 1988-1993 (Box R2751)
    - RF 85047 A 10 - Centre for African Family Studies - Management, evaluation and training, 1986-1992; 2 folders. (Box R2752)
    - RF 85049 A 24 - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Plasminogen activators and inhibitors, 1986-1990 (Box R2752)
    - RF 85049 A 27 - Prince of Songkla University - Sea urchin sperma proteins, 1987-1992 (Box R2752)
    - RF 85050 A 232 - Skinner, G. William, 1986-1991 (Box R2752)
    - RF 85076 - Foreign scholars' fellowship program on Soviet international behavior, 1985-1993 (Box R2752)
    - RF 86002 A 409 - Dartmouth College - Resident fellows, 1986-1992 (Box R2752)
    - RF 86002 A 411 - Wesleyan University (Middletown) - Resident fellows, 1986-1990, 1993 (Box R2752)
    - RF 86002 A 414 - Whitney Museum of American Art - Resident fellows, 1986-1989, 1993 (Box R2752)
    - RF 86002 A 416 - Institute for Advanced Study - Resident fellows, 1986-1992 (Box R2753)
    - RF 86011 A 43 - CardosodeAlmeida, MariaLucia, 1986-1993 (Box R2753)
    - RF 86039 - RF Research Fellowship Program for Minority Group scholars, 1977-1988; 2 folders. (Box R2753)
    - RF 86039 - RF Research Fellowship Program for Minority Group scholars - Evaluators, 1980-1983 (Box R2753)
    - RF 86039 A 133 - Rodriguez, Clara A., 1987-1989 (Box R2753)
    - RF 86039 A 141 - Stevens, Joseph H., Jr., 1987-1990 (Box R2754)
    - RF 86040 - Trade policy in developing countries, 1985-1989, 1992 (Box R2754)
    - RF 86040 A 4 - Fundacao Instituto de Pesquisas Economicas - Brazil and the new GATT round, 1986-1992 (Box R2754)
    - RF 86040 A 4 - Fundacao Instituto de Pesquisas Economicas - Brazil and the new GATT round - Supplementary material (Box R2754)
    - RF 86040 A 9 - Centre for Economic Policy Research (London) - Sub-Saharan Africa trade, 1985-1991 (Box R2754)
    - RF 86044 - Smithsonian Institution - Women in the progressive era conference, 1985-1992 (Box R2754)
    - RF 86052 - Urban Institute - Reagan budget cuts and non-profit organizations, 1981-1992; 4 folders. (Box R2755)
    - RF 86052 - Urban Institute - Reagan budget cuts and non-profit organizations, 1981-1992; 3 folders. (Box R2756)
    - RF 86055 - Lehrman Institute - Developing countries, 1986-1992 (Box R2756)
    - RF 86056 - Overseas Development Institute - Money supply and credit in developing countries, 1986-1993 (Box R2757)
    - RF 86060 - Rice Biotechnology Priorities, 1986-1990, 1993 (Box R2757)
    - RF 86060 A 3 - World Grains and Oil Seeds Study, 1988 (Box R2757)
    - RF 86060 A 4 - Brown University - Agrobiological choices and opportunities for LDC's, 1988-1991 (Box R2757)
    - RF 86060 A 5 - Priorities in Rice Biotechnology for East India, 1989-1990 (Box R2757)
    - RF 86061 A 12 - Indian Statistical Institute - Modern rice technology, 1987-1993 (Box R2757)
    - RF 86063 - Great Neglected Diseases of the Developing World, 1977-1988; 3 folders. (Box R2757)
    - RF 86063 - Great Neglected Diseases of the Developing World, 1977-1988; 2 folders. (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 142 - Case Western Reserve University - Entamoeba histolytica, 1986-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 143 - London School of Hygiene (and Tropical Medicine) - Leprosy reactions, 1986-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 145 - UniversityofWashington - Tuberculosis diagnosis and prevention, 1986-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A147 - Weizmann Institute of Science - S. mansoni and E. histolytica, 1987-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 148 - Mahidol University - Antimalarial development, 1986-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 149 - Hall Institute - Schistosomiasis vaccines, 1986-1989 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 150 - University of Stockholm - Malaria vaccines construction, 1986-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86063 A 152 - University of Virginia - Diarrheas and visceral leishmaniasis in Brazil, 1986-1990 (Box R2758)
    - RF 86064 - Clinical Epidemiology Resource and Training, 1985 (Box R2759)
    - RF 86064 A 8 - Clinical Epidemiology Resource and Training Centers - INCLEN presidential search, 1990-1991 (Box R2759)
    - RF 86065 - Population Council, Inc., 1968-1993; 4 folders. (Box R2759)
    - RF 86065 - Population Council, Inc., 1968-1993; 1 folder. (Box R2760)
    - RF 86065 - Population Council, Inc. - Supplementary material, 2 folders. (Box R2760)
    - RF 86066 A 17 - University of Nairobi - Health benefits of contraceptive counseling, 1987-1992 (Box R2760)
    - RF 86066 A 18 - Asociacion Dominicana Pro-Bienesta de la Familia, Inc. - Low dose gossypol study, 1987-1991 (Box R2760)
    - RF 86067 A 12 - Institut de Formation et de Recherche Demographiques (IFORD) - Research, 1985-1993 (Box R2761)
    - RF 86067 A 14 - University of Dar es Salaam - Demography and Community Health, 1986-1993 (Box R2761)
    - RF 86067 A 18 - Omari, Cuthbert Kashingo, 1986-1988, 1992 (Box R2761)
    - RF 86057 A 26 - University of Ghana - Maternal education, 1987-1992 (Box R2761)
    - RF 86083 - Makerere University, 1986-1993 (Box R2761)
    - RF 86083 A 4 - Makerere University - Micro Computers, 1988-1989, 1992-1993 (Box R2761)
    - RF 86083 A 6 - Makerere University - Makerere Institute of Social Research, 1987-1988, 1990-1991 (Box R2761)
    - RF 87001 A 9 - Ssekamatte-Ssebuliba, John B., 1987-1992 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87001 A 13 - Mararo, Bucyalimwe, 1987-1992 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87001 A 15 - Bah, Tierno Siradiou, 1987-1993 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87001 A 17 - Mugangu; Trinto Enama, 1988-1993 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87001 A 19 - Naty, Alexander, 1988-1992 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87005 A 59 - Raghavan, K. Vijay, 1987-1993 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87008 A 13 - Ministry of Public Health of China - Nuerovirulence testing/training program, 1985-1989 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87012 A 420 - Cornell University - Resident fellows (Southeast Asia), 1987-1992 (Box R2762)
    - RF 87012 A 420 - Cornell University - Resident fellows (Southeast Asia) - Supplementary material (Box R2762)
    - RF 87012 A 424 - University of Texas - Medical School (Galveston) - Resident fellows, 1985-1991; 2 folders. (Box R2763)
    - RF 87026 - Tropical Forestry, 1986-1991 (Box R2763)
    - RF 87026 A 1 - Peruvian Foundation for the Conservation of Nature - Peru conservation data center, 1986-1992 (Box R2763)
    - RF 87026 A 1 - Peruvian Foundation for the Conservation of Nature - Peru conservation data center - Supplementary material (Box R2763)
    - RF 87028 - University of London - Fellowships in health planning and financing, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box R2764)
    - RF 87031 A 17 - Gujarat Institute of Area Planning - Family planning services, 1987-1992 (Box R2764)
    - RF 87031 A 22 - University of Nairobi - Family planning, 1986-1992 (Box R2764)
    - RF 87038 A 48 - University of Minnesota - Gjerdingen and Froberg, 1987-1991 (Box R2764)
    - RF 87038 A 58 - Kiecolt K., Jill, 1987-1990 (Box R2764)
    - RF 87056 A 248 - Pennsylvania State University - Women's fertility in Colombia, 1988-1992 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87056 A 249 - Simmons, Ruth, 1988-1992 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87056 A 251 - Garcia Guzman, Brigida, 1988-1991 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87056 A 254 - Christenson, Bruce Allan, 1988-1992 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87057 A 4 - Rice Biotechnology Programs in China and India - Training, 1987-1991 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87058 A 64 - Yale University - Rice genes for carotenoid biosynthesis, 1987-1993 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87069 A 37 - Nigerian Institute of Social and Economic Research - Female migration to urban centers in Nigeria, 1987-1992 (Box R2765)
    - RF 87069 A 39 - University of Malawi - Family size in Malawi, 1987-1992 (Box R2766)
    - RF 87069 A 40 - Union for African Population Studies - Regional collaboration, 1988-1991 (Box R2766)
    - RF 87069 A 50 - University of Nairobi - Population Studies Research Institute - Microcomputer laboratory, 1986-1993 (Box R2766)
    - RF 87074 - University of Sussex - Science and technology in developing countries, 1987-1992 (Box R2766)
    - RF 88001 A 3 - University of Zimbabwe - Tropical soil biology and fertility program, 1987-1990 (Box R2766)
    - RF 88003 - Impact of Agricultural Technical Change, 1986-1992; 2 folders. (Box R2766)
    - RF 88003 A 28 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Modern Rice Technology in China, 1990-1992 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88003 A 30 - Research on Rice in India - Publication, 1990-1991 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88007 A 170 - Mahidol University - Clinical epidemiology - Jariya, 1989 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88007 A 171 - Mahidol University - Clinical Epidemiology - Narong, 1989 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88009 A 20 - Assiut University - Vaginal contraceptive pill study, 1987-1992 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88009 A 22 - University of Nairobi - Vaginal contraceptive pill study, 1987-1989 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88009 A 23 - African Fertility Society - AIDS research, 1988-1992 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88009 A 31 - University of Ibadan - Vaginal contraceptive pill study, 1987-1992 (Box R2767)
    - RF 88010 - International Institute for Strategic Studies - International Security, 1973-1992; 1 folder. (Box R2767)
    - RF 88010 - International Institute for Strategic Studies - International Security, 1973-1992; 1 folder. (Box R2768)
    - RF 88010 - International Institute for Strategic Studies - International Security - Supplementary material, 4 folders. (Box R2768)
    - RF 88013 A 434 - Johns Hopkins University - Resident Fellows (Art and Anthropology), 1988-1992 (Box R2769)
    - RF 88013 A 434 - Johns Hopkins University - Resident Fellows (Art and Anthropology) - Supplementary material (Box R2769)
    - RF 88013 A 439 - Wayne State University - Resident fellows, 1984-1992 (Box R2769)
    - RF 88013 A 439 - Wayne State University - Resident fellows - Supplementary material (Box R2769)
    - RF 85013 A 440 - Newberry Library - Resident fellows, 1984-1993 (Box R2769)
    - RF 88013 A 441 - Harvard University - Divinity School - Women's Studies, 1979-1993 (Box R2769)
    - RF 88013 A 441 - Harvard University - Divinity School - Women's Studies, 1979-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2770)
    - RF 88025 - Independent Sector - Giving and Volunteering in America, 1987-1992 (Box R2770)
    - RF 88036 - Illuminating intergenerational perspectives, 1987-1992 (Box R2770)
    - RF 88036 A7 - Harvard Universi'ty - Family Support and Education Initiatives, 1987-1992 (Box R2770)
    - RF 88036 A 8 - American Association for Marriage and Family Therapy Research and Education Foundation Inc. - Child Care, 1988-1990 (Box R2770)
    - RF 88036 A 9 - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research - Policy seminars, 1990-1991 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 37 - Chanco, Seshi Victor, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 39 - Kiragu, karungari R., 1988-1992 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 44 - Ogundimu, Folu, 1988-1991 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 50 - Taha, Taha El Tahir, 1988-1991 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 60 - Laki, Sam L., 1988-1992 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 64 - Ye, Henri Yazome, 1988-1993 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 70 - Njoya, Aboubakar, 1987-1993 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88038 A 74 - Sineshaw, Tilahun, 1989-1992 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88040 - Genetic Map of Rice, 1986-1990 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88040 A 11 - University of Pennsylvanfa - DNA Cloning Methods, 1989-1992 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88040 A 12 - International Rice Research Institute - Plant Breeding, 1990 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88044 A 65 - Ottawa Civic Hospital, 1988-1992 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88044 A 69 - Chiba University - Gossypol effects on type A spermatogonia, 1989-1993 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88044 A 70 - Cornell University - Gossypol and cancer in women, 1987-1991 (Box R2771)
    - RF 88048 A 75 -O'Neill, June, 1980-1992 (Box R2772)
    - RF 88048 A 76 - Eisenstein, Hester, 1989-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88048 A 77 - Shields, Stephanie, 1989-1991 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88048 A 83 - England, Paula, 1988-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88048 A 85 - Klatch, Rebecca E., 1988-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88048 A 86- Moeller, Robert, 1989-1991 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88054 - National Bureau of Economic Research - Latin American-U.S. collaborations, 1987-1991 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88056 - National Polytechnic Institute (Mexico City) - Research with CIMMYT, 1987-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88057 A 3 - Washington State University - Protein inhibitor genes, 1989-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88058 A 30 - Kelly, Timothy G., 1988-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88058 A 31 - Swindale, Anne Jenniger, 1988-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 67 - Zhu Zhen, 1988-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 68 - Kang, Seorig-Mo, 1985-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 70 - Martinez de la Escalera, Gonzalo, 1988 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 71 - Hong Guo-Fang, 1985-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 73 - Xie Weidong, 1988-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 74 - Wang Linfang, 1984-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 77 - Choudary, Prabhakara V., 1986-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 78 - Uadia, Patrick Ojeifo, 1989-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 79 - Riazuddin, Sheikh, 1989-1992 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 83 - Rao, C. Durga, 1988-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 84 - Khan, Iqrar Ahmad, 1989-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 85 - Zhang Zhiwen, 1989 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88061 A 86 - Le Trang, Nguyen, 1989-1990 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88072 A 4 - Council on Foreign Relations - Africa and U.S. policy, 1989-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88072 A 10 - Foundation for the Study of Independent Social Ideas - Dissentissue on Africa, 1990-1993 (Box R2773)
    - RF 88073 - Beyond child survival, 1987-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2774)
    - RF 88073 A 1 - Cornell University - Beyond child survival secretariat, 1989-1991 (Box R2774)
    - RF 88073 A 6 - Beyond child survival - Program studies, 1989-1992 (Box R2774)
    - RF 88075 A 44 - Ninsin, Kwame Akon, 1986-1991 (Box R2774)
    - RF 88078 A 56 - University of Yaounde - Reproductive biology course, 1989-1991 (Box R2774)
    - RF 88078 A 57 - University of Zimbabwe - Fellowships in Population Studies, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box R2774)
    - RF 88078 A 61 - Union for African Population Studies - Migration and development conferences (Box R2775)
    - RF 88078 A 61 - Union for African Population Studies - Migration and development conferences - Supplementary material, 1989-1991 (Box R2775)
    - RF 88079 A 256 - Chavez Alarcon, Noe, 1988-1993 (Box R2775)
    - RF 88079 A 258 - University of Washington - Status of women and fertility in Iran, 1987-1991 (Box R2775)
    - RF 88079 A 262 - Pong, Suet-ling, 1989-1992 (Box R2775)
    - RF 88080 - Global Committee of Parliamentarians on Population and Development - Leaders' awareness of population policies, 1988-1992 (Box R2775)
    - RF 88081 - Pan American Health Organization - Biotechnology in Latin America, 1986-1993 (Box R2776)
    - RF 88083 - United Nations - World Health Organizanization - Poor Women and Children, 1987-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2776)
    - RF 88083 - United Nations - World Health Organizanization - Poor Women and Children - Supplementary material (Box R2776)
    - RF 88090 A 5 - Rural Development Administration, Korea - Rice Research, 1984-1992 (Box R2777)
    - RF 88090 A 5 - Rural Development Administration, Korea - Rice Research - Supplementary material (Box R2777)
    - RF 88090 A 13 - Redwood Records Cultural and Educational Fund - Collaborative Caribbean poetry, music and choreography, 1989-1991 (Box R2777)
    - RF 88092 A 17 - Painted Bride Art Center - "Latin Vibrations! at the Bride", 1989-1993 (Box R2777)
    - RF 88094 - American Council of Learned Societies - American National Biography, 1987-1992 (Box R2777)
    - RF 89014 A 449 - University of North Carolina - Resident fellows, 1986-1993 (Box R2778)
    - RF 89025 A 88 - Kansas State University- Molecular Biology of rice storage proteins, 1984-1992 (Box R2778)
    - RF 89025 A 89 - Washington University - Rice Yellow Mottle Virus, 1989-1992 (Box R2778)
    - RF 89025 A 92 - Purdue University - Rice Plant Regeneration, 1989-1992 (Box R2778)
    - RF 89025 - Kansas State University - Rice, 1985-1993 (Box R2778)
    - RF 89025 A 95 - University of Ghent - Rice genetic transformation, 1984-1991 (Box R2778)
    - RF 89025 A 100 - Pennsylvania State University - "Oryza Sativa", 1990-1992 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89026 A 38 - RF Collaboration on Rice Biotechnology Book, 1989-1993 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89026 A 43 - Gnanamanickam, Samuel S., 1990-1992 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89026 A 46 - Zhu Lihuang, 1988-1992 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89027 - Plant Biotechnology in Developing Countries, 1989-1991 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89027 A 2 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Chemical Use in Asian Rice Paddies, 1988-1992 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89027 A 4 - InternationalServiceforNationalAgriculturalResearch-Chinese System, 1989-1993 (Box R2779)
    - RF 89027 A 11 - Montana State University - Environmental costs of chemicals in Asian rice paddies, 1988-1992 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89027 A 13 - Thailand Development Research Institute Foundation - Rice research analysis in Thailand, 1991-1994 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 207 - Ohio State University - Drug and Vaccine Use, 1989-1992 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 209 - Chulalongkorn University - Measels immunization among slum children, 1990-1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 216 - University of Rio de Janeiro - Colposcopic biopsy, 1990-1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 222 - University of Health Sciences - Cefuroxime for Bacterial Meningitis, 1990-1991 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 223 - University of Health Sciences - Comparative drug treatment for seizures, 1989-1990 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 224 - Chulalongkorn University - Master Degree Program in Health Development, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 226 - University of North Carolina - Vargas Dissertation (Chapel Hill), 1989-1991 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89028 A 228 - Universidad de la Frontera - Tri-cyclic Antidepressants and Theumatoid Arthritis, 1990-1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 40 - University of Chile - Acrosome reaction in human sperm, 1989-1990 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 45 - Alexandria University - Male fertility, 1990-1991 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 46 - Institute of Biology and Experimental Medicine (Buenos Aires) - Testicular steroido-genesis regulation, 1990-1992 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 47 - North-Eastern Hill University (India) - Gonadal cells and Hormonotoxins, 1989-1991 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 49- Catholic University (Chile) - Ciliarymovement in fallopian lube, 1990-1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 53 - CEMICAMP - Oocyte maturation in humans, 1991-1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89033 A 54 - University of Dar es Salaam - Burundi refugee child mortality, 1991-1993 (Box R2780)
    - RF 89034 A 82 - Nyong'o, Risper N., 1988-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 84 - Hasler, Richard, 1988-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 90 - Cisse, Sekou, 1989-1991 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 92 - Mayekiso, Monde, 1988-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 100 - Deng Kuol, Biong, 1988-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 104 - Annan, Isaac Billy, 1988-1991 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 111 - Sylaa, Soriba, 1988-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 116 - Wabwire-Mangen, Fred, 1988-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 118 - Zinnah, Moses Monroe, 1989-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 120 - Kebede, Yohannes, 1989-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 122 - Hamid, Gamal M., 1989-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 126 - Ngoh, Lucy N., 1989-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 129 - Mafela, Lily, 1989-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 131 - Rabfu, Safianu, 1989-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 133 - Masflela, Sipho T.B., 1989-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 135 - Berisso, Taddesse, 1989-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 139 - Shompole, Patrick Sankale, 1990-1992 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 143 - Gatongi, Peter Maina, 1990-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 145 - Thiam, Amadou Khoudiedji, 1990-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 147 - Zaongo, Christophe G. L., 1990-1993 (Box R2781)
    - RF 89034 A 149 - Nyamulinda, Vincent, 1989-1992 (Box R2782)
    - RF 89034 A 151 - Gemeda, Guluma, 1989-1992 (Box R2782)
    - RF 89045 - Arms Control Association - International security, 1976-1992; 3 folders. (Box R2782)
    - RF 89045 - Arms Control Association - International security - Supplementary material, 2 folders. (Box R2782)
    - RF 89046 - Institute for East-West Security Studies - Seeking security in the 1990s, 1988-1993 (Box R2783)
    - RF 89055 A 32 - Ayuk, Elias Takor, 1989-1993 (Box R2783)
    - RF 89055 A 34 - Hassan, Rashid Mekki, 1988-1992 (Box R2783)
    - RF 89055 A35 - Fuglie, Keith Owen, 1988-1992 (Box R2783)
    - RF 89055 A 37 - Field, Les W., 1987-1993 (Box R2783)
    - RF 89055 A 41 - Delehanty, James Matthew, 1987-1993 (Box R2783)
    - RF 89055 A 44 - Amuah, Alexander Kojo, 1990-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89055 A 45 - Mbabu, Adiel Nkonge, 1988-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 87 - An, Chung Sun, 1985, 1989-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 88 - Barreto De Castro, Luiz, 1989-1990 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 89 - Rumjanek, Franklin David, 1985-1992 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 90 - Rasool, Nassar B.G., 1984-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 91 - Wang Xian, 1989-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 92 - Soridelli, Daniel O., 1989-1992 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 94 - Yang Jinshui, 1990 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 95 - Mayorga, Luis S., 1990-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 96 - Satz, Marcos Leonardo, 1990 (Box R2784)
    - RF S9057 A 97 - Sultana Ahmed, Khalida, 1990-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 98 - Rodriguez, Luis Leandro, 1989-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 99 - Elegbede, John Abiodun, 1988-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 101 - Tripathy, Baishnab Charan, 1990-1993 (Box R2784)
    - RF 89057 A 102 - Muniyappa, K., 1990-1993 (Box R2785)
    - RF 89057 A 103 - Vijayraghavan, Usha, 1990-1992 (Box R2785)
    - RF 89057 A 107 - Kan Beki, 1990 (Box R2785)
    - RF 89057 A 125 - Datta, Asis, 1986-1993 (Box R2785)
    - RF 89058 A 16 - TransferofTechnology.- Group of Experts Meeting, 1984-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2785)
    - RF 89062 A 4 - Centro Medico A.S.I.A. (Ecuador) - HIV seroprevelance in prostitutes, 1989-1992 (Box R2785)
    - RF 89062 A 6 - American Foundation for AIDS Research - African technical assistance workshop, 1989-1992 (Box R2785)
    - RF 85006 - Microform libraries for Medical Schools and Research units in the Developing World, 1986-1993 (Box R2873)
    - RF 85006 - Microform libraries for Medical Schools and Research units in the Developing World, 1981-1985 (Box R2874)
    - RF 85006 - Microform libraries for Medical Schools and Research units in the Developing World - Supplementary material (Box R2874)
    - RF 85011 - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Low Dose Gossypol Study, 1986-1990 (Box R2874)
    - RF 85013 A 403 - Rutgers University - Resident Fellows, 1984-1991 (Box R2874)
    - RF 85013 A 404 - College of Physicians of Philadelphia - Resident Fellows, 1984-1991, 1994 (Box R2875)